DAVID EISENMENGER

UX DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

A user experience designer with a diverse background in healthcare, social work, and nonprofit managment. My focus is to help create seamless user experiences that work well, make people happy, and add value to the product. I have an extensive history focused on wellbeing in the user's experience.

CONTACT

101 Stevenson Ave Louisville, KY 40206

502.468.4978 david@heronblue.design www.heronblue.design

SKILLS

Research

Interview

Survey

Comparative Analysis
Usability Testing

Design

Persona

Journey Mapping
Wireframing

Prototyping

Tools

Sketch

Adobe Creative Suite

InVision

Languages

HTML/CSS JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

HeronBlue Design Freelance Designer

Dec 2017 - Present

Front end web development and user experience design for clients. Developed initial web presence for economic empowerment organization EmpowerWest. Increased original views to site by 200%.

Friendship Health and Rehab

Feb 2016 - Present

Director of Social Services

Focus on customer wellbeing and family user experience. CMS facility star rating increased from one to three stars Feb 2016 to present.

Signature Healthcare

May 2013 - Feb 2016

Director of Education Research and Programming

Design, development, and deployment of education and training programs. Directed three company wide initiatives serving a network of 113 healthcare facilities. Trained 200 company leaders in program that increased student EQ by 15%

Signature Healthcare

Oct 2009 - May 2013

Director of Spirituality

Led initiatives focused on patient and staff wellbeing. Received Community Outreach Award for program connection patient and the community. CMS Deficiency free annual surveys 2012, 2013.

EDUCATION

User Experience Design Course

May 2018 - Oct 2018

Springboard

Front End Web Development Track

Sept 2017 - Mar 2018

Code Louisville

M.A. Marriage and Family Therapy Louisville Presbyterian Theological Seminary Aug 2005 - May 2007

B.A. Peace and Global Studies

Aug 1999 - May 2001

Earlham College